pranhub.com 2011-06-02

# Privacy Policy | Latest Articles – Submit FREE Articles & Press Release

PRANHub.com respects the privacy of its users and are committed to protect the information of its Users. We, at PRANHub.com believes that you have the right to know our practices regarding the information we may collect, use and disclose when you visit pranhub.com.

**Acceptence:** BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS MENTIONED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.

**Information PRANHub.com Collects**  
PRANHub.com generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our newsletter, or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Some optional information may also be requested.

**How PRANHub.com Uses Information Provided By You**  
PRANHub.com uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our newspapers, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you your newsletter. Similarly, we may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, to personalize your experience on the site, to provide you with certain information and services available only to registered users, and to identify you when conducting customer service operations. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While PRANHub.com will seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, PRANHub.com does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. There may also be occasion when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

**Cookies**  
You may have read about “cookies,” nuggets of information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. For example, if you register on any part of PRANHub.com you can opt to save your user name and password on your computer. We can provide this convenience by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies. Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

If you don’t want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of PRANHub.com may not function properly.

While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

**IP Address**  
Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, gather broad demographic information, and administer our Web site.

**Change in Policy**  
The terms of this Privacy Policy will govern the use of the Site and any information collected therein. Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time, so please re-visit this page frequently. In case of any material change, we will post a clear notice on the Site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Update” and your continued use of the Site on or after the Last Update date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, you can send us an email via our [Contact Us](http://www.pranhub.com/contact-us/) Page.
